<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Lyne Moser</title><link>https://lynemoser.com/</link><description>Recent content on Lyne Moser</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://lynemoser.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://lynemoser.com/research/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lynemoser.com/research/</guid><description>Preprints Dec. 2023 (∞,n)-Limits I: Definition and first consistency results Joint with Nima Rasekh, and Martina Rovelli, arXiv:2312.11101 Aug. 2023 Internal Grothendieck construction for enriched categories Joint with Maru Sarazola, and Paula Verdugo, arXiv:2308.14455 July 2023 An (∞,n)-categorical straightening-unstraightening construction Joint with Nima Rasekh, and Martina Rovelli, arXiv:2307.07259 Jun. 2023 A model structure for Grothendieck fibrations Joint with Maru Sarazola, arXiv:2306.11076 Feb. 2023 A homotopy coherent nerve for (∞,n)-categories Joint with Nima Rasekh, and Martina Rovelli, arXiv:2208.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://lynemoser.com/seminar/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lynemoser.com/seminar/</guid><description>Seminar: Topics in (∞,2)-categories During the Summer semester 2023, I organized a seminar on Topics in (∞,2)-categories. We had an overview of different models of (∞,2)-categories, as well as some constructions thereof, such as the Gray tensor product and (∞,2)-limits. We also considered some applications of (∞,2)-category theory in derived algebraic geometry, topological quantum field theory, and K-theory.
Here is a detailed program of the seminar.
April 19 2-categories and double categories Benedikt Froehlich April 26 (∞,1)-categories and enriched models of (∞,2)-categories Jana Nickel May 3 Model of complete Segal $\Theta_2$-spaces Marco Giustetto May 10 Models of double ∞-categories and 2-fold complete Segal spaces Divya Ghanshani May 17 Model of scaled simplicial sets Jana Nickel May 24 Gray tensor product for 2-categories Vikram Nadig May 31 Gray tensor product for (∞,2)-categories Jun Xu June 7 Universal property of the (∞,2)-category of correspondences Johannes Glossner June 14 Limits in a 2-category Lyne Moser June 21 The fully extended 2-dimensional cobordism hypothesis Pier-Federico Pacchiarotti June 28 Six functor formalism Johannes Glossner July 5 Functoriality of the stable $A_1$-homotopy category Niklas Kipp July 12 Limits in an (∞,2)-category Nima Rasekh July 19 K-theory via double categories Maru Sarazola</description></item><item><title/><link>https://lynemoser.com/talks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lynemoser.com/talks/</guid><description>Talks Dec. 2023 Subfactors and Fusion (2-)Categories, Banff International Research Station, Canada 2-Limits and 2-terminal objects are too different Nov. 2023 Atlantic Category Theory Seminar, Dalhousie University, Halifax, Canada Representation theorem for enriched categories Nov. 2023 Séminaire d&amp;rsquo;Homotopie et Géométrie Algébrique, Université Paul Sabatier, Toulouse, France Defining limits in (∞,n)-categories Oct. 2023 Séminaire de Théorie des Catégories, Université catholique de Louvain, Belgium Model structures for double categories Oct. 2023 Homotopy Theory day, New York University Abu Dhabi, UAE Model structures for double categories July 2023 International Category Theory Conference (CT2023), Université catholique de Louvain, Belgium New methods for contructing model categories Jun.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://lynemoser.com/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lynemoser.com/contact/</guid><description>Email: lyne.moser@ur.de Current affiliation Universität Regensburg
Universitätsstraße 31 93053 Regensburg Germany</description></item></channel></rss>