<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Lyne Moser</title><link>https://lynemoser.com/</link><description>Recent content on Lyne Moser</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://lynemoser.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://lynemoser.com/research/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lynemoser.com/research/</guid><description>Publications and preprints July 2023 An (∞,n)-categorical straightening-unstraightening construction Joint with Nima Rasekh, and Martina Rovelli, arXiv:2307.07259 Jun. 2023 A model structure for Grothendieck fibrations Joint with Maru Sarazola, arXiv:2306.11076 Feb. 2023 A homotopy coherent nerve for (∞,n)-categories Joint with Nima Rasekh, and Martina Rovelli, arXiv:2208.02745 Jan. 2023 Fibrantly-induced model structures Joint with Léonard Guetta, Maru Sarazola, and Paula Verdugo, arXiv:2301.07801 Sep. 2022 2-limits and 2-terminal objects are too different Joint with tslil clingman In: Applied Categorical Structures.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://lynemoser.com/seminar/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lynemoser.com/seminar/</guid><description>Seminar: Topics in (∞,2)-categories During the Summer semester 2023, I&amp;rsquo;m organizing a seminar on Topics in (∞,2)-categories. We will have an overview of different models of (∞,2)-categories, as well as some constructions thereof, such as the Gray tensor product and (∞,2)-limits. We will also see some applications of (∞,2)-category theory in derived algebraic geometry, topological quantum field theory, and K-theory.
The seminar will take place on Wednesdays from 10:15-11:45 in room M009 and on zoom.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://lynemoser.com/talks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lynemoser.com/talks/</guid><description>Talks Jul. 2023 International Category Theory Conference (CT2023), Université catholique de Louvain, Belgium New methods for contructing model categories Jun. 2023 Homotopy Theory in Trondheim, NTNU, Trondheim, Norway Straightening-unstraightening for (∞, n)-categories Jun. 2023 Seminar: Topics in (∞,2)-categories, Universität Regensburg, Germany Limits in a 2-category Feb. 2023 Geometry and Topology Seminar, UMass Amherst, US Nerve for 2-dimensional categories Dec. 2022 YaMCATS, University of Manchester, UK Representation theorem for enriched categories Nov.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://lynemoser.com/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lynemoser.com/contact/</guid><description>Email: lyne.moser@ur.de Current affiliation Universität Regensburg
Universitätsstraße 31 93053 Regensburg Germany</description></item></channel></rss>